​​
Bold text.​
Italic text.​
Underlined text.​
Times New Roman.​
72px font size.​
(Font size must be more than double the style's size to take affect.)​
Diagonally moving subtitles.​
(Unfortunately, YouTube's subtitle FPS is very poor,
thus it is very jittery when it comes to movement.)​
Diagonally moving subtitles.​
Red font.​
48px font size, with vertical movement.​
Secondary style with preset configuration.​
Ba​​sic karaoke timing.​
Basic ​​karaoke timing.​
Basic ka​​raoke timing.​
Basic kara​​oke timing.​
Basic karao​​ke timing.​
Basic karaoke ​​timing.​
Basic karaoke ti​​ming.​
Basic karaoke timing.​
Basic fade with 200ms in/out.​
Vertical text. This gets interesting.​
Shaking subtitles.​
Chromatic aberration.​
S​​tching karaoke for your viewing pleasure.​
Gli​​tching karaoke for your viewing pleasure.​
Glis​​karaoke for your viewing pleasure.​
Glitching ​​karaoke for your viewing pleasure.​
Glitching ka​​raoke for your viewing pleasure.​
Glitching kaK​​oke for your viewing pleasure.​
Glitching karao​​ke for your viewing pleasure.​
Glitching karaoL​​for your viewing pleasure.​
Glitching karaoke ​​for your viewing pleasure.​
Glitching karaoke S​​your viewing pleasure.​
Glitching karaoke for ​​your viewing pleasure.​
Glitching karaoke for l​​viewing pleasure.​
Glitching karaoke for your ​​viewing pleasure.​
Glitching karaoke for your u​​ing pleasure.​
Glitching karaoke for your view​​ing pleasure.​
Glitching karaoke for your viewu​​pleasure.​
Glitching karaoke for your viewing ​​pleasure.​
Glitching karaoke for your viewing M​​sure.​
Glitching karaoke for your viewing plea​​sure.​
Glitching karaoke for your viewing pleam​
Glitching karaoke for your viewing pleasure.​
Packed text.​
Many​
subtitles​
all​
at​
once!​
!!!​
Subscript text.​
Superscript text.​
Custom text background and colour.​
Unfortunately, there is no rotation/rotation animation
that is available to be used at the moment.​
You will have to live with unicode upside-down characters.​
Gradual font size increase to 72px.​
Yellow subtitles fading to cyan in a 2000ms timespan.​
Can't think of anything else to display. Hope this helped!
.ASS and .VTT files are available to download in desc.​